Guide to the Jewish Community Council of Greater Washington records, 1937-1988 MS2012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- 2007 Accession, 1987-2004; MS2012 Series 6; 18 Linear feet
  - JCPA Plenum, 2003 (Box UP07-7, Folder 8)
  - JPDS - Jewish Primary Day School, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 9)
  - Green Folder, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 10)
  - MoCo Public Schools' Educators Symposium on Jewish Life, 2003 May 27 (Box UP07-7, Folder 11)
  - MoCo Public Schools' Educators Symposium on Jewish Life, 2002 May 28 (Box UP07-7, Folder 12)
  - MCPS Educators Symposium 2001-2002, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 13)
  - Educators Symposium Evaluation form, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 14)
  - 2 MCPS Educators Symposium on Jewish Life, 2001 May 17 (Box UP07-7, Folder 15)
  - Security Forum - 2002 (FBI), undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (school), undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 18)
  - Muslim/Interfaith Materials, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 19)
  - MJA, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 20)
  - MILC, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 21)
  - National Issues/Congress, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 22)
  - Neighborhood Partnership Program, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 23)
  - For Adrienne Mandel - Transportation, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 24)
  - Washington Leadership Summit, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 25)
  - Sudan, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 26)
  - Grants (misc.), undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 27)
  - MD Holocaust Museum Tour, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 28)
  - Israel, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 29)
  - Federal Issues, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 30)
  - JSSA, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 31)
  - Hate Crimes, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 32)
  - Housing, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 33)
  - JCPA, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 34)
  - JDC, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 35)
  - JCA, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 36)
  - Medicaid Issues, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 37)
  - MHA Legislative Alerts, undated (Box UP07-7, Folder 38)
  - Super Sunday, 2002 (Box UP07-8, Folder 1)
  - Super Sunday, 1999 (Box UP07-8, Folder 2)
  - Super Sunday, 1998 (Box UP07-8, Folder 3)
  - Super Sunday, 2001 (Box UP07-8, Folder 4)
  - Budget - Montgomery County, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 5)
  - Budget - State, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 6)
  - Bond Bills, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 7)
  - Community Sve. Grants, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 8)
  - CDBG: FY2004, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 9)
  - CDBG, 2002 (Box UP07-8, Folder 10)
  - 2003 Legislative Reception, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 11)
  - Absentee Ballot Info, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 12)
  - Advertising/Transportation etc., undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 13)
  - AIM, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 14)
  - Anti-Council emails, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 15)
  - Gun Control, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 16)
  - DC, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 17)
  - Death Penalty/Capital Punishment, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 18)
  - Death Penalty - MD Report, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 19)
  - Eyal, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 20)
  - Advocacy Day, 2003 (Box UP07-8, Folder 21)
  - Board, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 22)
  - Carefirst, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 23)
  - Mont. Co. Council Tour, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 24)
  - Children's Health, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 25)
  - "Good News" Ruling, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 26)
  - Council At-Large Candidates Forum, undated (Box UP07-8, Folder 27)
  - Morella - Van Hollen Debate, 2002 October 24 (Box UP07-8, Folder 28)
  - Holocaust Oral History Course cassette tapes, undated (Box UP07-9, Folder 1)
  - Cassette tapes, undated (Box UP07-9, Folder 2)
  - Montgomery Video Productions Jewish News In Review, undated (Box UP07-9, Folder 3)
  - Jewish News In Review VHS, undated (Box UP07-9, Folder 4)
  - Social Action: Grassroots Style - Jewish Comm. Hr. VHS, 1987 March 13 (Box UP07-9, Folder 5)
  - Jewish News In Review Fuji Film 33, undated (Box UP07-9, Folder 6)
  - Jewish News In Review - Big Tapes, undated (Box UP07-9, Folder 7)
  - Cassettes, undated (Box UP07-10, Folder 1)
  - White box of slides, undated (Box UP07-10)
  - Navy box of slides, undated (Box UP07-10)
  - Israel Pocket Library - Jewish Values, undated (Box UP07-10, Folder 4)
  - Battleground - Facts and Fantasy in Palestine, undated (Box UP07-10, Folder 5)
  - Jewish News In Review - Maxell 66/33, undated (Box UP07-10, Folder 6)
  - Jewish News In Review - FUJIFILM 33, undated (Box UP07-10, Folder 7)
  - Jewish News In Review - Maxell 126/33, undated (Box UP07-10, Folder 8)
  - Reels, undated (Box UP07-10, Folder 9)
  - Misc. VHS, undated (Box UP07-10, Folder 10)
  - Jewish News In Review - VHS, undated (Box UP07-11)
  - Jewish News In Review - Big Tapes, undated (Box UP07-11)
  - Projector Slides, undated (Box UP07-12)